[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This celebrity had a twin brother who died at birth.", "correct_answer": "Elvis Presley", "incorrect_answers": ["Madonna", "Michael Jackson", "Elton John"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This monastic egghead pioneered the study of genetics, which eventually explained the mechanisms of speciation through genetic mutation. Who is the \u201cfather of modern genetics?\u201d", "correct_answer": "Gregor Mendel", "incorrect_answers": ["James Watson", "Jean-Baptiste Lamarck", "Francis Crick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Monopoly money has been used in popular culture to refer to which of these types of currencies?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Currencies that cannot be used to purchase services on the free market", "Currencies in which each paper bill is in different color", "Currencies that cannot be used to purchase goods on the free market"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long has Kyle Gass (KG) been trying to become a famous musician in the movie Tenacious D?", "correct_answer": "15 years", "incorrect_answers": ["all his life", "12 year", "10 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Scarlett Johansson marry Canadian actor Ryan Reynolds?", "correct_answer": "in 2008", "incorrect_answers": ["in 2005", "in 2006", "in 2004"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nuclear fusion is the production of energy from the splitting of certain atoms.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of coffee is forbidden by which one of the following religions?", "correct_answer": "The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints", "incorrect_answers": ["Islam", "Ethiopian Orthodox Christianity", "The Sufi Branch of Islam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Worldwide, tropical cyclone activity peaks towards the end of which season and why?", "correct_answer": "Summer, because water temperatures are warmest", "incorrect_answers": ["Spring, due to the rapid worming of water", "Fall, as temperature rapidly falls, waters remain warm", "Winter, due to the delta between air and water temperatures"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Solve for X:\nX = [(number of arms on a squid) - (height in feet of an NBA basketball hoop)] * [number of minutes taken for light from the sun to reach the earth]", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "24", "72"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sweets are stored by an Internet browser?", "correct_answer": "Cookies", "incorrect_answers": ["Biscuits", "Candy bars", "Chocolates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these physiological features does the chinchilla lack?", "correct_answer": "The ability to sweat", "incorrect_answers": ["The ability to sneeze", "The ability to jump", "The ability to swallow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of his own body does Prince Charming from the Shrek movies adore the most?", "correct_answer": "His hair", "incorrect_answers": ["His lips", "His butt", "His eyes"]}]